holivine.com 2011-05-07

# Holivine.com

Welcome to Holivine.com!

**HOLIVINE.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

 **Please Read the Following and Understand**

Your privacy is important to Holivine.com and we take our responsibility seriously to protect the data that you provide us in the normal course of interacting with our site. Therefore, we have developed the comprehensive privacy policy below to help you better understand what data we collect and how we use it.  
 **Customer and Membership Information:**

Customer account information and Membership account information that you provide (such as your email address, address, phone number, passwords, credit card or payment information, etc.) is held in strict confidence and will not be sold or rented t o 3rd parties, but will be used for the purposes of providing services described on this website. 

**Email Privacy:**  
**Email Newsletter & Email Alert Subscription Forms**

Holivine.com uses subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to email newsletters and/or email alerts based on their categories of interest. We collect contact information (like y our name and/or email address among other data) to provide you with the information that you request ed. We do not sell or rent email addresses to any 3rd parties. 

**Confirm OPT-IN**

We provide confirm opt-in opportunities for any email list(s) that you choose to receive. We use your email address to confirm your subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to any Holivine.com email list or newsletter. You can change the email address that you have subscribed by using our Manage Your Subscriptions form or you can unsubscribe with the email address you're currently subscribed with and then subscribe again with a new email address. 

**Unsubscribe**

You can unsubscribe/opt-out for any or all email lists that you previously chose to receive. An email sent to you includes the information necessary for removal from the list. 

**Transactional Relationships**

Customers, Members, and/or Users are considered to be engaged in a transactional relationship with Holivine.com and as such, we may need to email or communicate with you from time to time in order to deliver our services. 

**Personal Information and Other Data We Collect:**

Holivine.com collects personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, etc. when you register for various services we provide (example: Creating a membership account). We may combine this data wit h other Holivine.com services or 3rd party data to provide a better user experience for you. 

Holivine.com uses cookies (a piece of data stored on the user's computer) and other technologies to provide you with a quality experience and to learn how you use our services so that we can innovate to improve our services. 

Holivine.com may record/log information automatically any time you interact with our site or use any of our products & services. This may include information such as your IP address, URL, browser type, domain name(s), access dates & times, operating system, country of origin, language type, page views and user sessions to help diagnose problems and/or deliver our services to you. 

**Uses:**

We may use the personal information you provided to provide the services you requested and for our own research and analysis to operate and improve on the services and product s that we deliver, as well as develop new services and products. 

We may share the aggregated non-personal information with 3rd parties outside of Holivine.com.   
When we use 3rd parties to assist us in the processing of your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policies, confidentiality and security measures.   
We may share information with 3rd parties in limited circumstances when complying with legal process, preventing suspected fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.   
We may use your postal and electronic address to send you items and/or information relevant to your use of our services.   
We may conduct member and/or user survey's in order to improve our services.   
**Advertising Specific Terms & Conditions: **

We use a 3rd party advertising company to serve our ads on our website and in our emails, based on personal information. To track the effectiveness of the ads and provide a better user experience, this company may use information about your web visits to our website to serve relevant ads. Information collected and used may include IP address, geographical location, their cookie and historical data previously collected. We will not provide any personal information to our advertisers when you interact with or view a targeted ad, however, by viewing or interacting with an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will assume you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad(s). 

**Security Management and Data Security:**

Holivine.com has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including management procedures and specialized training for those who work directly with our databases. We take measures to protect against the unauthorized access of personal data, including physical security considerations of the stored data. We restrict access to personal data to Holivine.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, innovate, and deliver our services. 

**Notification of Changes:**

From time to time, Holivine.com will occasionally update our Privacy Policy. If there are any material changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify via email and provide you the opportunity to opt-out prior to any substantial change that has been taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from Holivine.com you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. Holivine.com encourages you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy. 

**Legal Disclaimer:**

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our web site or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

| 

|   
---  
Using Myspace and Facebook to pick up stunning girls is easy! Follow our tips to make sure your profile is set to allow you to go out with many attractive girls. _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
As Haleys deadline approaches, your lover takes ideas to ensure that all her friends and family might be ready when time turns up. Brooke and Julian even prepare to get started on a family, although Chuck rotates to Pursuit for relax a problem. _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
As soon as Sagittarius and Pisces join together in a love match, a relationship of realized dreams is formed. Sagittarius is a lot more of the thinker and philosophizer, very easily drifting around from 1 pursuit on the next. Pisces is a lot more inward, _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Il film che state per vedere, caratteristiche rare, e fino ad ora filmati top secret dalla volta della CIA, di esperimenti di laboratorio condotti presso SRI con psichico Uri Geller. Questa capacita intuitiva e stato nominato (RV) Remote Viewing, e la ric _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
"Tree Hill is definitely a place anywhere in the world. Maybe it is a great deal like a person's earth. Maybe it's nothing like the item. Yet if you look closer, you might see someone including anyone. _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
How deliciously ironic it is. In 2002, Major League Baseball and Pizer officers have been along the way of deciding which participant can be provided the means to become the spokesperson for Sildenafil, which is Viagra. After rejecting Barry Bonds as a co _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Bingo can be a game of chance played by millions of folks across the globe. It was invented and played with the Italians four hundred eighty one years ago throughout the long period of Italian War . _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
It is vital that you just understand how one can enhance your web site traffic, however even more essential is having the ability to read your web site visitors statistics. With out understanding your website site visitors statistics, chances are you'll b _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
You will find several important elements you should think about when you publish Internet marketing review that sells. In this post I'll cover several quite crucial components of a successful Internet marketing review and the best way to apply it to your _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Dress shirts with company logo are an excellent way to advertise an organization or a company. They could bring a lot of benefits to an organization though establishing its brand identity. Logo embroidered dress shirts can influence positively the employe _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Video conferencing is available for personal or business use. Video conferencing is 1 component of teleconferencing, the others are audio conferencing, and data conferencing. Video conferencing will be the ideal answer for law firms, businesses and govern _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
glassine bags are made of glassine paper, which is a beautiful, plain paper, translucent that has multiple uses. glassine paper is made using a process called schedule. This process involves passing the raw paper rolls through multiple times to make the p _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Every beginning golfer needs some equipment essentials in order to really get started with the game of golf. _(read entire article)_   
  
---  
Mediterranean House Plans o Scenery tips and hints Mediterranean residence packages comes in conjunction with a superb theme on your gardening. The lawyer, you should definitely insert abundant facilities, such as palms, jasmine shrubs, and various _(read entire article)_
